gayscout.com 2018-12-21

# Data Privacy Statement · gayScout 2018

### Contact details

Tayton GmbH  
Schwerinstr. 15a  
10783 Berlin  
Deutschland

Email: info(at)tayton.net

Data protection has a very high priority. Therefore, as a user of our website, you hereby receive all necessary information about how and for what purpose we collect data about you and about we use it. 

### Legal basis of processing

Art. 6 I lit. a GDPR is the legal basis for processing operations where we obtain consent for a particular processing purpose. If the processing of personal data is necessary to fulfill a contract of which the data subject is a party, as is the case, for example, in processing operations necessary for the provision of any other service or consideration, the processing is based on Art. 6 I lit. b GDPR. The same applies to processing operations that are necessary to carry out pre-contractual measures, such as in cases of inquiries about our products or services. 

If our company is subject to a legal obligation that requires the processing of personal data, such as For the fulfillment of tax obligations, the processing is based on Art. 6 I lit. c GDPR. In rare cases, the processing of personal data may be required to protect the vital interests of the data subject or another natural person. This would be the case, for example, if a visitor to our premises were injured and his or her name, age, health insurance or other vital information would have to be passed on to a doctor, hospital or other third party. Then the processing would be based on Art. 6 I lit. d GDPR.

Ultimately, processing operations could be based on Art. 6 I lit. f GDPR. On this legal basis, processing operations that are not covered by any of the above legal bases are required if processing is necessary to safeguard the legitimate interests of our company or a third party, unless the interests, fundamental rights and fundamental freedoms of the person concerned prevail. Such processing operations are particularly allowed to us because they have been specifically mentioned by the European legislator. In that regard, it considered that a legitimate interest could be assumed if the data subject is a customer of the responsible person (recital 47 sentence 2 GDPR).

### Authorized interests in the processing that are being pursued by the controller or a third party

Is the processing of personal data based on Article 6 I lit. f GDPR is our legitimate interest in carrying out our club activities to fulfill our club purpose. 

### Duration of storage of personal data

The criterion for the duration of the storage of personal data is the respective statutory retention period. After the deadline, the corresponding data will be deleted, if they are no longer required to fulfill the contract or to initiate a contract.

### Legal or contractual provisions for the provision of personal data; Necessity for the conclusion of the contract; Obligation of the data subject to provide the personal data; possible consequences of non-provision

We clarify that the provision of personal information is in part required by law (such as tax regulations) or may result from contractual arrangements (such as details of the contractor). Occasionally it may be necessary for a contract to be concluded that an affected person provides us with personal data that must subsequently be processed by us. For example, the data subject is required to provide us with personal information when our company enters into a contract with her. Failure to provide the personal data would mean that the contract with the person concerned could not be closed.

For all questions and concerns concerning the correction, blocking or deletion of personal data, please contact the address stated in the imprint. 

A use of our internet pages is basically possible without any indication of personal data.

However, if you use special services through our website, processing of personal data may be required. The collection and use of your data is strictly in accordance with the provisions of the Federal Data Protection Act "Bundesdatenschutzgesetz" (BDSG) and the Telemedia Act "Telemediengesetz" (TMG). The collection of these personal data takes place on a voluntary basis, if this is possible for us. We will only share this information with third parties with your express consent. We ensure the security of your data with regard to your requests to us by using SSL encryption. At this point we point out the general dangers of internet use, which we have no influence on, because internet-based data transmissions can in principle have security gaps, so that an absolute protection can not be guaranteed on our part. Especially in e-mail traffic your data is not safe without further precautions and may be recorded by third parties. For this reason, you are free to transmit personal data to us in alternative ways, such as by phone or by post.

### Information, deletion, blocking, limitation of processing

At any time you will receive free information about the personal data we have stored about you as well as the origin, the recipient and the purpose of data collection and data processing. In addition, you have the right to request the correction, blocking or deletion of your data. This does not apply to data that is stored due to legal regulations or required for the proper conduct of business. If data is not recorded by a legal archiving obligation, we delete your data at your request. If the archiving obligation takes effect, we will block your data. If the storage purpose is deleted, the data will be deleted. 

If the accuracy of the data is disputed by the data subject, you have the right to request that the processing be restricted until the examination is completed in a reasonable time. Or we no longer need personal information for processing purposes, but the data subject requires them to assert, exercise or defend legal claims. Or the person concerned has objection to the processing conformable to art. 21 para. 1 GDPR and it is not yet clear whether the legitimate reasons for processing predominate.

### Collection of general data and information

Each time our website is accessed, our system collects a series of general data and information. This general data and information is stored in the log files of the server. It is possible to record the browser types and versions used, the operating system used by the accessing system, the website from which an accessing system accesses our website (so-called referrers), who access sub-web pages via an accessing system on our website, the date and time the time of access to the website, an Internet Protocol (IP) address, the accessing system's Internet service provider and other similar data and information used in the event of attacks on our information technology systems. 

When using this general data and information, we do not draw any conclusions about the data subject. Rather, this information is needed in order to correctly deliver the contents of our website, to optimize the content of our website and to advertise it, to ensure the long-term functioning of our information technology systems and the technology of our website, and to prosecute the law enforcement authorities in the event of a cyberattack To provide information. This anonymously collected data and information is therefore statistically and further evaluated with the aim of increasing data protection and data security in order to ultimately ensure the best possible level of protection for the personal data processed by us. The anonymous data of the server log files are stored separately from all personal data provided by an affected person.

### Third-party content and services

The offer on our website may also include content, services and services of other providers that complement our offer. Examples of such offers are maps from Google Maps, YouTube videos or graphic representations of third parties. Calling these services from third parties regularly requires the transmission of your IP address. This makes it possible for these providers to use their user IP address and also to save it. We make every effort to include only those third parties who use IP addresses solely to deliver the content. However, we have no influence on which third party provider may store the IP address. This storage can serve for statistical purposes, for example. In this context, please also note the special data protection statements for individual third-party providers and service providers whose services we use on our website. You will also find these in our privacy policy.

### Contact via the website

Due to legal regulations, this website contains information that enables fast electronic contact as well as direct communication with us, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address). If an affected person contacts the association by e-mail or via the contact form, the personal data transmitted by the person concerned will be automatically saved. Such voluntarily personal data is stored for purposes of processing or contacting the data subject. There is no disclosure of this personal data to third parties.

### Privacy Policy for use and use of other services provided by Google

For reasons of browser compatibility, Java Scripts (html5shiv) by Google Inc. are also used on this website. The integration takes place via an external server call from Google USA. This will tell the server which of the pages you visited. Furthermore, according to our information, the IP address of the browser of the visitor's device on this website is stored by Google. 

To protect their data sent via our contact forms, we use the service reCAPTCHA of the company Google Inc. (Google). The query is used to distinguish whether the input is made by a human or abusive by automated, mechanical processing. The query includes the sending of the IP address and any other data required by Google for the reCAPTCHA service to Google. For this purpose, your input will be transmitted to Google and used there. 

This website uses Google Maps to display interactive maps and create directions. Google Maps is a map service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, California 94043, USA. By using Google Maps, information about the use of this website, including your IP address and the (starting) address entered as part of the route planning function, can be transferred to Google in the USA. If you visit a website on our website that contains Google Maps, Your browser connects directly to Google's servers. The content of the map will be transmitted by Google directly to your browser and integrated into the website by Google. Therefore, we have no control over the amount of data Google collects in this way. 

The privacy policy posted by Google and YouTube, available at [ https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/DE/policies/privacy/) provide information on the collection, processing and use of personal data YouTube and Google.

### Privacy Policy on the use and use of ad servers

This website uses the Revive AdServer, a software for the provision and integration of advertisements. The Revive AdServer uses so-called "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website. Revive AdServer also uses counting pixels. Through this information about the traffic is recorded and analyzed. The data generated by cookies and pixels on the use of this website and the delivery of advertising formats are transmitted to the Revive AdServer and stored there. This information may be shared with contractors but will not be merged with your IP address. You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software. 

gayScout operates the named ad server itself. Accordingly, no personal or personally identifiable information is passed on to other companies.

Berlin, March 2018
